<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="EventInstance.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="fr-FR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-15c36f0" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">02cd5861-7ce2-4a82-b358-31f8435a0ac51d5923ea6f0adb7e9a29cff95c32d8b297910978.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1d5923ea6f0adb7e9a29cff95c32d8b297910978</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">04/03/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
      <xliffext:moniker_ids xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">netframework-4.5.1,netframework-4.5.2,netframework-4.5,netframework-4.6.1,netframework-4.6.2,netframework-4.6,netframework-4.7.1,netframework-4.7,xamarinmac-3.0</xliffext:moniker_ids>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>Represents language-neutral information for an event log entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Représente des informations indépendantes du langage pour une entrée du journal des événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>Use <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an event log entry with a resource identifier rather than a string value.</source>
          <target state="translated">Utilisez <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire une entrée de journal des événements avec un identificateur de ressource plutôt qu’une valeur de chaîne.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>To write an event log entry, initialize the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> property and pass the instance to the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> method.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour écrire une entrée de journal des événements, initialisez le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> propriété et passez l’instance à la <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> (méthode).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the instance identifier to find and display the corresponding string from the localized resource file based on current language settings.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise l’identificateur d’instance pour rechercher et afficher la chaîne correspondante à partir du fichier de ressource localisée selon les paramètres de langue actuels.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>You must register the event source with the corresponding resource file before you write events using resource identifiers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez inscrire la source d’événements avec le fichier de ressources correspondant avant d’écrire des événements à l’aide d’identificateurs de ressources.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>When writing events, you can set the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType%2A&gt;</ph> property to specify the icon that the Event Viewer displays for the entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Lorsque vous écrivez des événements, vous pouvez définir le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour spécifier l’icône que l’Observateur d’événements affiche pour l’entrée.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>You can also specify a <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> property to specify the category that the Event Viewer displays for the entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous pouvez également spécifier un <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour spécifier la catégorie que l’Observateur d’événements affiche pour l’entrée.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the category to filter events written by an event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise la catégorie pour filtrer les événements écrits par une source d’événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The Event Viewer can display the category as a numeric value, or it can use the category as a resource identifier to display a localized category string.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements peut afficher la catégorie en tant que valeur numérique, ou utiliser la catégorie comme identificateur de ressource pour afficher une chaîne de catégorie localisée.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>To display localized category strings in the Event Viewer, you must use an event source configured with a category resource file, and set the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> to a resource identifier in the category resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour afficher les chaînes de catégorie localisée dans l’Observateur d’événements, vous devez utiliser une source d’événement configuré avec un fichier de ressources de catégorie et définir le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> à un identificateur de ressource dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>If the event source does not have a configured category resource file, or the specified <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> does not index a string in the category resource file, and then the Event Viewer displays the numeric category value for that entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Si la source d’événements n’a pas un fichier de ressources de catégorie configuré ou spécifié <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> ne pas l’index une chaîne dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie, puis l’Observateur d’événements affiche la valeur de catégorie numérique pour cette entrée.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>Configure the category resource file, along with the number of category strings in the resource file, using the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogInstaller&gt;</ph> or the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData&gt;</ph> class.</source>
          <target state="translated">Configurer le fichier de ressources de catégorie, ainsi que le nombre de chaînes de catégorie dans le fichier de ressources, à l’aide de la <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogInstaller&gt;</ph> ou <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData&gt;</ph> classe.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>You must register a source for an event log before using <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an event with the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> method.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez inscrire une source d’un journal des événements avant d’utiliser <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire un événement avec le <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> (méthode).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="114" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The source must be configured for writing localized entries to the log and the source must define at least a message resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">La source doit être configurée pour écrire des entrées localisées dans le journal et la source doit définir au moins un fichier de ressources du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="115" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>Create the new event source during the installation of your application.</source>
          <target state="translated">Créer la source d’événements pendant l’installation de votre application.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="116" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>This allows time for the operating system to refresh its list of registered event sources and their configurations.</source>
          <target state="translated">Ainsi, le temps nécessaire au système d’exploitation à actualiser sa liste de sources d’événements inscrits et leurs configurations.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="117" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>If the operating system has not refreshed its list of event sources, and you attempt to write an event with the new source, the write operation will fail.</source>
          <target state="translated">Si le système d’exploitation n’a pas actualisé sa liste de sources d’événements, et que vous tentez d’écrire un événement avec la nouvelle source, que l’opération d’écriture échouera.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="118" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>You can configure a new source using an <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogInstaller&gt;</ph>, or using the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.CreateEventSource%2A&gt;</ph> method.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous pouvez configurer une nouvelle source en utilisant un <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogInstaller&gt;</ph>, ou à l’aide de la <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.CreateEventSource%2A&gt;</ph> (méthode).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="119" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>You must have administrative rights on the computer to create a new event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez disposer des droits d’administration sur l’ordinateur pour créer une source d’événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="120" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>For details about defining event messages and building event log resource files, see the "Message Compiler" topic in the Platform SDK documentation at <bpt id="p1">[</bpt><ph id="ph1">http://msdn.microsoft.com</ph><ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com)</ept>.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour plus d’informations sur la définition des messages d’événement et la création de fichiers de ressources du journal des événements, consultez la rubrique « Message Compiler » dans la documentation Platform SDK à <bpt id="p1">[</bpt> <ph id="ph1">http://msdn.microsoft.com</ph> <ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com)</ept>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="121" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The following code example writes an informational event entry, and then reuses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an entry for a warning event to an existing event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suivant écrit une entrée d’événement d’information, puis réutilise le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire une entrée pour un événement d’avertissement dans un journal des événements existant.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="122" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The event message text is specified using a resource identifier in a message resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le texte de message d’événement est spécifié à l’aide d’un identificateur de ressource dans un fichier de ressources du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="123" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The code example assumes that the corresponding message resource file has been registered for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suppose que le fichier de ressources du message correspondant a été enregistré pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="124" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The code example uses the following message text file, built into the resource library EventLogMsgs.dll.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code utilise le fichier texte du message suivant, incorporé dans la bibliothèque de ressources EventLogMsgs.dll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="125" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>A message text file is the source from which the message resource file is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un fichier texte du message est la source à partir de laquelle le fichier de ressource de message est créé.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="126" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>The message text file defines the resource identifiers and text for the category, event message, and parameter insertion strings.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le fichier texte de message définit les identificateurs de ressources et le texte de la catégorie, message d’événement et les chaînes d’insertion de paramètre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="127" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance">
          <source>Initializes a new instance of the <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance" /&gt;</ph> class using language-neutral information to define an event log entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Initialise une nouvelle instance de la classe <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance" /&gt;</ph> à l'aide d'informations indépendantes du langage pour définir une entrée de journal des événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="128" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>A resource identifier that corresponds to a string defined in the message resource file of the event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Identificateur de ressource qui correspond à une chaîne définie dans le fichier de ressources d'un message de la source d'événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="129" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>A resource identifier that corresponds to a string defined in the category resource file of the event source, or zero to specify no category for the event.</source>
          <target state="translated">Identificateur de ressource qui correspond à une chaîne définie dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie de la source d'événements ou zéro pour ne spécifier aucune catégorie pour l'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="130" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>Initializes a new instance of the <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance" /&gt;</ph> class using the specified resource identifiers for the localized message and category text of the event entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Initialise une nouvelle instance de la classe <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance" /&gt;</ph> à l'aide des identificateurs de ressource spécifiés pour le message localisé et le texte de catégorie de l'entrée d'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="131" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>To write an informational entry to an event log, initialize an <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> and pass it to the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> method.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour écrire une entrée d’information dans un journal des événements, initialisez une <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> et passer à la <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> (méthode).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="132" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>Set the <ph id="ph1">`instanceId`</ph> to the resource identifier of the event message in the corresponding <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.MessageResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> property for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Définir le <ph id="ph1">`instanceId`</ph> identificateur de ressource du message d’événement, qui correspond à <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.MessageResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="133" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>Set the <ph id="ph1">`categoryId`</ph> to a numeric category value, or the resource identifier of the event category in the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.CategoryResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> property for the source; set the <ph id="ph3">`categoryId`</ph> to zero for no event category.</source>
          <target state="translated">Définir le <ph id="ph1">`categoryId`</ph> à une valeur de catégorie numérique, ou l’identificateur de ressource de la catégorie d’événement dans le <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.CategoryResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour la source, l’ensemble du <ph id="ph3">`categoryId`</ph> à zéro pour la catégorie d’événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="134" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType%2A&gt;</ph> property for the new instance is set to <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType.Information&gt;</ph> by default.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType%2A&gt;</ph> pour la nouvelle instance est définie sur <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType.Information&gt;</ph> par défaut.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="135" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the resource identifiers to display the corresponding strings from the localized resource files for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise les identificateurs de ressource pour afficher les chaînes correspondantes à partir de fichiers de ressources localisés pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="136" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>You must register the source with the corresponding resource files before you can write events using resource identifiers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez inscrire la source avec les fichiers de ressources correspondants avant d’écrire les événements à l’aide d’identificateurs de ressources.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="137" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The following code example writes an informational event entry, and then reuses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an entry for a warning event to an existing event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suivant écrit une entrée d’événement d’information, puis réutilise le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire une entrée pour un événement d’avertissement dans un journal des événements existant.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="138" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The event message text is specified using a resource identifier in a message resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le texte de message d’événement est spécifié à l’aide d’un identificateur de ressource dans un fichier de ressources du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="139" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The code example assumes that the corresponding message resource file has been registered for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suppose que le fichier de ressources du message correspondant a été enregistré pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="140" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The code example uses the following message text file, built into the resource library EventLogMsgs.dll.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code utilise le fichier texte du message suivant, incorporé dans la bibliothèque de ressources EventLogMsgs.dll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="141" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>A message text file is the source from which the message resource file is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un fichier texte du message est la source à partir de laquelle le fichier de ressource de message est créé.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="142" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The message text file defines the resource identifiers and text for the category, event message, and parameter insertion strings.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le fichier texte de message définit les identificateurs de ressources et le texte de la catégorie, message d’événement et les chaînes d’insertion de paramètre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="143" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="instanceId" /&gt;</ph> parameter is a negative value or a value larger than <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt32.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le paramètre <ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="instanceId" /&gt;</ph> est une valeur négative ou une valeur supérieure à <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt32.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="144" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>-or-</source>
          <target state="translated">- ou -</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="145" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32)">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="categoryId" /&gt;</ph> parameter is a negative value or a value larger than <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt16.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le paramètre <ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="categoryId" /&gt;</ph> est une valeur négative ou une valeur supérieure à <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt16.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="146" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>A resource identifier that corresponds to a string defined in the message resource file of the event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Identificateur de ressource qui correspond à une chaîne définie dans le fichier de ressources d'un message de la source d'événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="147" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>A resource identifier that corresponds to a string defined in the category resource file of the event source, or zero to specify no category for the event.</source>
          <target state="translated">Identificateur de ressource qui correspond à une chaîne définie dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie de la source d'événements ou zéro pour ne spécifier aucune catégorie pour l'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="148" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>An <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> value that indicates the event type.</source>
          <target state="translated">Valeur <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> indiquant le type de l'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="149" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>Initializes a new instance of the <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance" /&gt;</ph> class using the specified resource identifiers for the localized message and category text of the event entry and the specified event log entry type.</source>
          <target state="translated">Initialise une nouvelle instance de la classe <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance" /&gt;</ph> à l'aide des identificateurs de ressource spécifiés pour le message localisé, le texte de catégorie de l'entrée d'événement et le type d'entrée du journal des événements spécifié.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="150" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>To write an entry to an event log, initialize an <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> and pass it to the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> method.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour écrire une entrée dans un journal des événements, initialisez une <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> et passer à la <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog.WriteEvent%2A&gt;</ph> (méthode).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="151" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>Set the <ph id="ph1">`instanceId`</ph> to the resource identifier of the event message in the corresponding <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.MessageResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> property for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Définir le <ph id="ph1">`instanceId`</ph> identificateur de ressource du message d’événement, qui correspond à <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.MessageResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="152" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>Set the <ph id="ph1">`categoryId`</ph> to a numeric category value, or the resource identifier of the event category in the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.CategoryResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> property for the source; set the <ph id="ph3">`categoryId`</ph> to zero for no event category.</source>
          <target state="translated">Définir le <ph id="ph1">`categoryId`</ph> à une valeur de catégorie numérique, ou l’identificateur de ressource de la catégorie d’événement dans le <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.CategoryResourceFile%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour la source, l’ensemble du <ph id="ph3">`categoryId`</ph> à zéro pour la catégorie d’événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="153" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the resource identifiers to display the corresponding strings from the localized resource files for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise les identificateurs de ressource pour afficher les chaînes correspondantes à partir de fichiers de ressources localisés pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="154" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>You must register the source with the corresponding resource files before you can write events using resource identifiers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez inscrire la source avec les fichiers de ressources correspondants avant d’écrire les événements à l’aide d’identificateurs de ressources.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="155" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>Set the <ph id="ph1">`entryType`</ph> to one of the pre-defined entry types.</source>
          <target state="translated">Définir le <ph id="ph1">`entryType`</ph> à un des types d’entrées prédéfinis.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="156" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the event type to determine which icon to display in the list view of the event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise le type d’événement pour déterminer l’icône à afficher dans la vue liste du journal des événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="157" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The following code example writes two audit event entries to the event log <ph id="ph1">`myNewLog`</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suivant écrit deux entrées d’événements dans le journal des événements d’audit <ph id="ph1">`myNewLog`</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="158" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The code example creates a new event source and a new event log if they do not exist on the local computer.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code crée une source d’événement et un journal des événements s’ils n’existent pas sur l’ordinateur local.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="159" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The event message text is specified using a resource identifier in a resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le texte de message d’événement est spécifié à l’aide d’un identificateur de ressource dans un fichier de ressources.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="160" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The code example uses the following message text file, built into the resource library EventLogMsgs.dll.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code utilise le fichier texte du message suivant, incorporé dans la bibliothèque de ressources EventLogMsgs.dll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="161" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>A message text file is the source from which the message resource file is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un fichier texte du message est la source à partir de laquelle le fichier de ressource de message est créé.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="162" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>The message text file defines the resource identifiers and text for the category, event message, and parameter insertion strings.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le fichier texte de message définit les identificateurs de ressources et le texte de la catégorie, message d’événement et les chaînes d’insertion de paramètre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="163" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source><ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="entryType" /&gt;</ph> is not a valid <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> value.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="entryType" /&gt;</ph> n’est pas une valeur de <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> valide.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="164" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source><ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="instanceId" /&gt;</ph> is a negative value or a value larger than <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt32.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="instanceId" /&gt;</ph> est une valeur négative ou une valeur supérieure à <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt32.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="165" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source>-or-</source>
          <target state="translated">- ou -</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="166" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.#ctor(System.Int64,System.Int32,System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType)">
          <source><ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="categoryId" /&gt;</ph> is a negative value or a value larger than <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt16.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="categoryId" /&gt;</ph> est une valeur négative ou une valeur supérieure à <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt16.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="167" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>Gets or sets the resource identifier that specifies the application-defined category of the event entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Obtient ou définit l'identificateur de ressource qui spécifie la catégorie d'entrée d'événement définie par l'application.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="168" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>A numeric category value or resource identifier that corresponds to a string defined in the category resource file of the event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Valeur de catégorie numérique ou identificateur de ressource qui correspond à une chaîne définie dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie de la source d'événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="169" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The default is zero, which signifies that no category will be displayed for the event entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">La valeur par défaut est zéro, ce qui signifie qu'aucune catégorie ne sera affichée pour l'entrée d'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="170" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>Event log categories are application-defined values that help filter events, or provide further information about the event.</source>
          <target state="translated">Catégories du journal des événements sont des valeurs définies par l’application qui aident à filtrer des événements ou fournissent davantage d’informations sur l’événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="171" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>For example, your application can define separate categories for different components or different operations.</source>
          <target state="translated">Par exemple, votre application peut définir des catégories séparées pour des composants différents ou des opérations différentes.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="172" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>Set the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> property to specify the category that the Event Viewer displays for the entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Définir le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> propriété pour spécifier la catégorie que l’Observateur d’événements affiche pour l’entrée.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="173" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The Event Viewer can display the category as a numeric value, or it can use the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> as a resource identifier to display a localized category string based on the current language settings.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements peut afficher la catégorie en tant que valeur numérique, ou elle peut utiliser le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> en tant que ressource identificateur pour afficher une chaîne de catégorie localisée basé sur les paramètres de langue actuel.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="174" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>To display localized category strings in the Event Viewer, you must use an event source configured with a category resource file, and set the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> to a resource identifier in the category resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour afficher les chaînes de catégorie localisée dans l’Observateur d’événements, vous devez utiliser une source d’événement configuré avec un fichier de ressources de catégorie et définir le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> à un identificateur de ressource dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="175" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>If the event source does not have a configured category resource file, or the specified <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> does not index a string in the category resource file, and then the Event Viewer displays the numeric category value for that entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Si la source d’événements n’a pas un fichier de ressources de catégorie configuré ou spécifié <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> ne pas l’index une chaîne dans le fichier de ressources de catégorie, puis l’Observateur d’événements affiche la valeur de catégorie numérique pour cette entrée.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="176" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>You must register the source with the corresponding resource file before you write event categories using resource identifiers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez inscrire la source avec le fichier de ressources correspondant avant d’écrire des catégories d’événements à l’aide d’identificateurs de ressources.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="177" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>Configure the category resource file, along with the number of category strings in the resource file, using the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogInstaller&gt;</ph> or the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData&gt;</ph> class.</source>
          <target state="translated">Configurer le fichier de ressources de catégorie, ainsi que le nombre de chaînes de catégorie dans le fichier de ressources, à l’aide de la <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogInstaller&gt;</ph> ou <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData&gt;</ph> classe.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="178" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>When defining category strings in a resource file, the category resource identifiers must be numbered consecutively starting at 1, up to the configured <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.CategoryCount%2A&gt;</ph> property value.</source>
          <target state="translated">Lorsque vous définissez les chaînes de catégorie dans un fichier de ressources, les identificateurs de ressource de catégorie doivent être numérotées consécutivement en commençant à 1, jusqu'à configuré <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventSourceCreationData.CategoryCount%2A&gt;</ph> valeur de propriété.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="179" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>Event categories are optional.</source>
          <target state="translated">Catégories d’événements sont facultatifs.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="180" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>If your application does not use categories, do not set the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> for the event log entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Si votre application n’utilise pas de catégories, ne définissez pas le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId%2A&gt;</ph> pour l’entrée de journal des événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="181" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>For details about defining event messages and building event resource files, see the "Message Compiler" topic in the Platform SDK documentation at <bpt id="p1">[</bpt><ph id="ph1">http://msdn.microsoft.com</ph><ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/)</ept>. For details about defining event categories in resource files, see the "Event Categories" topic in the Platform SDK</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour plus d’informations sur la définition des messages d’événement et la création de fichiers de ressources d’événement, consultez la rubrique « Message Compiler » dans la documentation Platform SDK à <bpt id="p1">[</bpt> <ph id="ph1">http://msdn.microsoft.com</ph> <ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/)</ept>. Pour plus d’informations sur la définition des catégories d’événements dans les fichiers de ressources, consultez la rubrique « Catégories d’événements » dans le Kit de développement de plate-forme</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="182" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The following code example writes an informational event entry, and then reuses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an entry for a warning event to an existing event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suivant écrit une entrée d’événement d’information, puis réutilise le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire une entrée pour un événement d’avertissement dans un journal des événements existant.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="183" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The event message text is specified using a resource identifier in a message resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le texte de message d’événement est spécifié à l’aide d’un identificateur de ressource dans un fichier de ressources du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="184" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The code example assumes that the corresponding message resource file has been registered for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suppose que le fichier de ressources du message correspondant a été enregistré pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="185" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The code example uses the following message text file, built into the resource library EventLogMsgs.dll.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code utilise le fichier texte du message suivant, incorporé dans la bibliothèque de ressources EventLogMsgs.dll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="186" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>A message text file is the source from which the message resource file is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un fichier texte du message est la source à partir de laquelle le fichier de ressource de message est créé.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="187" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The message text file defines the resource identifiers and text for the category, event message, and parameter insertion strings.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le fichier texte de message définit les identificateurs de ressources et le texte de la catégorie, message d’événement et les chaînes d’insertion de paramètre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="188" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.CategoryId">
          <source>The property is set to a negative value or to a value larger than <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt16.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated">La propriété est définie avec une valeur négative ou avec une valeur supérieure à <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt16.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="189" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>Gets or sets the event type of the event log entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Obtient ou définit le type d'événement de l'entrée du journal des événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="190" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>An <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> value that indicates the event entry type.</source>
          <target state="translated">Valeur <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> indiquant le type d'entrée d'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="191" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The default value is <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType.Information" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated">La valeur par défaut est <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="F:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType.Information" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="192" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>Each event is of a single type, which the application indicates when it reports the event.</source>
          <target state="translated">Chaque événement possède un type unique indiqué par l’application lorsqu’elle signale l’événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="193" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the event type to determine which icon to display in the list view of the event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise le type d’événement pour déterminer l’icône à afficher dans la vue liste du journal des événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="194" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The following code example writes an informational event entry, and then reuses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an entry for a warning event to an existing event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suivant écrit une entrée d’événement d’information, puis réutilise le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire une entrée pour un événement d’avertissement dans un journal des événements existant.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="195" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The event message text is specified using a resource identifier in a message resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le texte de message d’événement est spécifié à l’aide d’un identificateur de ressource dans un fichier de ressources du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="196" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The code example assumes that the corresponding message resource file has been registered for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suppose que le fichier de ressources du message correspondant a été enregistré pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="197" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The code example uses the following message text file, built into the resource library EventLogMsgs.dll.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code utilise le fichier texte du message suivant, incorporé dans la bibliothèque de ressources EventLogMsgs.dll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="198" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>A message text file is the source from which the message resource file is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un fichier texte du message est la source à partir de laquelle le fichier de ressource de message est créé.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="199" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The message text file defines the resource identifiers and text for the category, event message, and parameter insertion strings.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le fichier texte de message définit les identificateurs de ressources et le texte de la catégorie, message d’événement et les chaînes d’insertion de paramètre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="200" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.EntryType">
          <source>The property is not set to a valid <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> value.</source>
          <target state="translated">La propriété n'a pas une valeur <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="T:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType" /&gt;</ph> valide.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="201" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>Gets or sets the resource identifier that designates the message text of the event entry.</source>
          <target state="translated">Obtient ou définit l'identificateur de ressource qui désigne le texte du message de l'entrée d'événement.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="202" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>A resource identifier that corresponds to a string defined in the message resource file of the event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Identificateur de ressource qui correspond à une chaîne définie dans le fichier de ressources d'un message de la source d'événements.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="203" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> property uniquely identifies an event entry for a configured event source.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> propriété identifie de façon unique une entrée d’événement pour une source d’événement configuré.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="204" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>For events defined in message resource files, the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> corresponds to the resource identifier compiled from the message definition fields in the message text file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour les événements définis dans les fichiers de ressources du message, le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> correspond à l’identificateur de ressource compilé à partir des champs de définition de message dans le fichier texte du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="205" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>Your application can write localized event log entries by setting the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> to a resource identifier.</source>
          <target state="translated">Votre application peut écrire des entrées de journal des événements localisées en définissant le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> à un identificateur de ressource.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="206" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The Event Viewer uses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> resource identifier to find and display the corresponding string from the localized resource file based on current language settings.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’Observateur d’événements utilise le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId%2A&gt;</ph> identificateur de ressource pour rechercher et afficher la chaîne correspondante du fichier de ressources localisé en fonction des paramètres de langue actuel.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="207" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>You must register the source with the corresponding resource file before you write events using resource identifiers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Vous devez inscrire la source avec le fichier de ressources correspondant avant d’écrire des événements à l’aide d’identificateurs de ressources.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="208" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>For details about defining event messages and building event log resource files, see the "Message Compiler" topic in the Platform SDK documentation at <bpt id="p1">[</bpt><ph id="ph1">http://msdn.microsoft.com</ph><ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/)</ept>. For details about event log identifiers, see the "Event Identifiers" topic in the Platform SDK.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pour plus d’informations sur la définition des messages d’événement et la création de fichiers de ressources du journal des événements, consultez la rubrique « Message Compiler » dans la documentation Platform SDK à <bpt id="p1">[</bpt> <ph id="ph1">http://msdn.microsoft.com</ph> <ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/)</ept>. Pour plus d’informations sur les identificateurs du journal des événements, consultez la rubrique « Identificateurs d’événement » dans le Kit de développement de plate-forme.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="209" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The following code example writes an informational event entry, and then reuses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> to write an entry for a warning event to an existing event log.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suivant écrit une entrée d’événement d’information, puis réutilise le <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance&gt;</ph> pour écrire une entrée pour un événement d’avertissement dans un journal des événements existant.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="210" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The event message text is specified using a resource identifier in a message resource file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le texte de message d’événement est spécifié à l’aide d’un identificateur de ressource dans un fichier de ressources du message.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="211" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The code example assumes that the corresponding message resource file has been registered for the source.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code suppose que le fichier de ressources du message correspondant a été enregistré pour la source.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="212" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The code example uses the following message text file, built into the resource library EventLogMsgs.dll.</source>
          <target state="translated">L’exemple de code utilise le fichier texte du message suivant, incorporé dans la bibliothèque de ressources EventLogMsgs.dll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="213" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>A message text file is the source from which the message resource file is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un fichier texte du message est la source à partir de laquelle le fichier de ressource de message est créé.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="214" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The message text file defines the resource identifiers and text for the category, event message, and parameter insertion strings.</source>
          <target state="translated">Le fichier texte de message définit les identificateurs de ressources et le texte de la catégorie, message d’événement et les chaînes d’insertion de paramètre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="215" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="P:System.Diagnostics.EventInstance.InstanceId">
          <source>The property is set to a negative value or to a value larger than <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt32.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</source>
          <target state="translated">La propriété est définie avec une valeur négative ou avec une valeur supérieure à <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="F:System.UInt32.MaxValue" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>